Guide to the Records of the Tisch School of the Arts 1956-1981 (Bulk 1965-1981) RG 35
New York University Archives
- ACCESSION 93-025
  - Series V: Administrative Files
    - Winder, Bayly, Dean Faculty Arts and Science, 1972-1973 (Box 31, Folder 12)
    - Anthology of Film Archives, 1974 (Box 31, Folder 13)
    - Arts Development Associates, Joseph Wesley Zeigler, 1973-1974 (Box 31, Folder 14)
    - B - General, 1970-1974 (Box 31, Folder 15)
    - Bernstein, Leonard, 1968-1970 (Box 31, Folder 16)
    - C - General, 1970-1974 (Box 31, Folder 18)
    - California Institute of Arts, 1971-1973 (Box 31, Folder 19)
    - City Center Cinematheque Committee, 1971-1972 (Box 31, Folder 20)
    - City Center Cinematheque Committee, 1973-1974 (Box 31, Folder 21)
    - City Center of Music and Drama, 1971-1972 (Box 31, Folder 22)
    - City Center of Music and Drama, 1973-1974 (Box 31, Folder 23)
    - Daucher, Hans, Professor Universitaet Muenchen, 1973 (Box 31, Folder 24)
    - Duffey, Gordon, Director Interact Theatre Workshop, 1968-1974 (Box 31, Folder 25)
    - E - General, 1972-1973 (Box 31, Folder 26)
    - F - General, 1971-1974 (Box 31, Folder 27)
    - Film Society of Lincoln Center, 1972-1973 (Box 31, Folder 28)
    - Film Society of Lincoln Center, 1974 (Box 31, Folder 29)
    - Ford Foundation, 1969-1974 (Box 31, Folder 30)
    - Frankel, Gene, Mercer Arts Center, 1972 (Box 31, Folder 31)
    - G - General, 1971-1973 (Box 31, Folder 32)
    - Guggenheim Memorial Foundation Fellowship, 1971-1974 (Box 31, Folder 33)
    - H - General, 1971-1973 (Box 31, Folder 34)
    - Hagel, Raymond, Chair Board of MacMillan & Co., 1973-1974 (Box 31, Folder 35)
    - I - General, 1971-1973 (Box 31, Folder 36)
    - International Council of Fine Arts Deans (ICFAD), 1971-1972 (Box 31, Folder 37)
    - JDR 3rd Fund, 1973 (Box 31, Folder 38)
    - K - General, 1971-1974 (Box 31, Folder 39)
    - Kresge Foundation (incl. Alfred P. Sloan Foundation), 1969-1970 (Box 32, Folder 1)
      bar code#: 3 1142 04226083 9
    - Kresge Foundation, 1971 (Box 32, Folder 2)
    - Kresge Foundation, 1972-1974 (Box 32, Folder 3)
    - John F. Kennedy Center, 1971-1973 (Box 32, Folder 4)
    - L - General, 1972 (Box 32, Folder 5)
    - Lincoln Center, 1969-1973 (Box 32, Folder 6)
    - M - General, 1974 (Box 32, Folder 7)
    - Management of Arts New Program, 1972 (Box 32, Folder 8)
    - McCormick, Ken, Doubleday Inc., 1969-1974 (Box 32, Folder 9)
    - Metropolitan Opera, 1971-1972 (Box 32, Folder 10)
    - Miscellaneous, 1974-1975 (Box 32, Folder 11)
    - Misc. Correspondence - mostly to/from D. Oppenheim, 1966-1969 (Box 32, Folder 12)
    - Misc. Correspondence - mostly to/from D. Oppenheim, 1970-1971 (Box 32, Folder 13)
    - N - General, 1971-1974 (Box 32, Folder 14)
    - National Science Foundation, 1972-1973 (Box 32, Folder 15)
    - National Endowment for the Arts and Humanities, 1971-1974 (Box 32, Folder 16)
    - New York State Commission on Cultural Resources, 1971 (Box 32, Folder 17)
    - New York State Council on Arts, 1969-1974 (Box 32, Folder 18)
    - P - General, 1971-1974 (Box 32, Folder 19)
    - R - General, 1971-1973 (Box 32, Folder 20)
    - Rockefeller Foundation, 1969-1970 (Box 32, Folder 21)
    - Rockefeller Foundation, 1971-1972
    - Rockefeller Foundation, 1973-1974 (Box 32, Folder 22)
    - S - General, 1971-1974 (Box 32, Folder 24)
    - Social Science Research Council, 1973 (Box 32, Folder 25)
    - Sterling Manhattan Cable, 1971 (Box 32, Folder 26)
    - T - General, 1971-1974 (Box 32, Folder 27)
    - Theatre for Ideas, 1971 (Box 32, Folder 28)
    - U - General, 1972-1973 (Box 32, Folder 29)
    - University of Massachusetts (incl. D. Oppenheim's visit), 1971, 1974 (Box 32, Folder 30)
    - University of Toronto (incl. Stravinsky Colloquium), 1971 (Box 32, Folder 31)
    - "V", "W", "Y" - General, 1971-1973 (Box 32, Folder 32)
    - Young Audiences, 1969-1971 (Box 32, Folder 33)
    - Young Audiences, 1972-1974 (Box 32, Folder 34)
    - Admissions, NYU Office of, Herbert B. Livesey, Director, 1975-1976 (Box 33, Folder 1)
      bar code#: 3 1142 04226084 7
    - Advertising, Mary Katherine Stillwell, Frank Lopez, 1974-1975 (Box 33, Folder 2)
    - Advertising, Mary Katherine Stillwell, 1976 (Box 33, Folder 3)
    - Alternative Media Center, Nat'l Science Foundation, NYU-Reading Consortium, 1975-1977 (Box 33, Folder 4)
    - Alternative Media Center workbook (Box 33, Folder 5)
    - Alumni List (preparations work file), 1975-1976 (Box 33, Folder 6)
    - Awards, SOA students, 1976 (Box 33, Folder 7)
    - Bi-Centennial, NYU Committee G. Winchester Stone, Chair, 1974-1976 (Box 33, Folder 8)
    - Bi-Centennial, NYU Committee, Jane Maggin, Chair, 1975-1976 (Box 33, Folder 9)
    - Bromberg, Dr. Eleazer, Deputy Chancellor NYU, 1974-1975 (Box 33, Folder 10)
    - Budget - Bundy Aid, Whiteside Memo, 1975 (Box 33, Folder 11)
    - Buildings, Paul Stone, Manager, 1974-1976 (Box 33, Folder 12)
    - Calendar - D.Oppenheim - events, meetings, invitations, 1973-1974 (Box 33, Folder 13)
    - Calendar - D. Oppenheim - events, meetings, invitations, 1975 (Box 33, Folder 14)
    - Calendar - D.Oppenheim - events, meetings, invitations, 1976-1977 (Box 33, Folder 15)
    - Calendar - D.Oppenheim - misc. meeting materials, 1975-1976 (Box 33, Folder 16)
    - Commission on Graduate Planning, Feb.1974-Dec.1974 (Box 33, Folder 17)
    - Commission on Graduate Planning, Jan.1975-Feb.1976, 1975-1976 (Box 33, Folder 18)
    - Commission of Student Evaluation of Faculty, 1974 (Box 33, Folder 19)
    - Course Information Sheets, SOA Departments, Spring '76, 1976 (Box 33, Folder 20)
    - Course Information Sheets, SOA Departments, Fall '76., 1976 (Box 33, Folder 21)
    - Course Information Sheets, SOA Departments, Summer '76, 1976 (Box 33, Folder 22)
    - Dept. of Acting - memos D.Oppenheim./Omar Shapli; Shapli/anyone, 1975-1976 (Box 33, Folder 23)
    - Dept. of Cinema Studies, 1975-1976 (Box 33, Folder 24)
    - Dept. of Cinema Studies - memos D.Oppenheim/B. Simon; Simon/ anyone, 1975-1976 (Box 33, Folder 25)
    - Dept. of Dance - memos from/to Stuart Hodes, undated (Box 33, Folder 27)
    - Dept. of Drama, Undergraduate, 1976 (Box 33, Folder 28)
    - Dept. of Drama, Undergrad - Sue Flakes Audition Tour, 1975-76, 1975-1976 (Box 33, Folder 29)
    - Dept. of Drama, Undergrad - memos D.Oppenheim/S. Flakes; Flakes/anyone, 1975-1976 (Box 33, Folder 30)
    - Dept. of Drama, Undergrad - memos D.Oppenheim/Y. Simonides; Simonides/anyone, 1976 (Box 33, Folder 31)
    - Department of Film and T.V., Graduate, 1975-1976 (Box 33, Folder 32)
    - Advertising, Mary Katherine Stillwell, Frank Lopez, 1976-1977 (Box 34, Folder 1)
      bar code#: 3 1142 04226085 4
    - Advisory Council List, 1977-1978 (Box 34, Folder 2)
    - B - General, 1974-1976 (Box 34, Folder 3)
    - Budget, 1976-1977 (Box 34, Folder 4)
    - Budget - Departments, 1976 (Box 34, Folder 5)
    - Budget - Estimates, 1976-1979 (Box 34, Folder 6)
    - Budget - Memos to/from Claxton, Hoover, 1974-1975 (Box 34, Folder 7)
    - Budget - Memos to/from Claxton, Hoover, 1976 (Box 34, Folder 8)
    - Budget - Memos to Claxton, proposed SOA budget, 1975-1977 (Box 34, Folder 9)
    - Budget - Memos to/from Bing Claxton, Hoover, 1977 (Box 34, Folder 10)
    - Budget - Memos to/from Bing, Claxton, Hoover, 1978 (Box 34, Folder 11)
    - Budget - Memos from Joseph Eugene, 1975-1977 (Box 34, Folder 12)
    - Budget Policy Advisory Committee Meeting, 10/9/75, 1975 (Box 34, Folder 13)
    - Buildings - Central Plaza (2nd Ave.), P.Stone, Manager, 1975-1976 (Box 34, Folder 14)
    - Buildings - SOA, Shepard Strum, Manager, 1976-1978 (Box 34, Folder 15)
    - Buildings - Theft and Security, 1974-1976 (Box 34, Folder 16)
    - C - General, 1974-1976 (Box 34, Folder 17)
    - City Center of Music and Drama, 1975-1976 (Box 34, Folder 18)
    - Commencement, 1975-1976 (Box 34, Folder 19)
    - Commencement (incl. D. Oppenheim's Commencement speech), 1977 (Box 34, Folder 20)
    - Dept. of Design - memos D. Oppenheim/L. Burlingame; Burlingame/ anyone, 1974-1976 (Box 34, Folder 21)
    - Dept. of Design - Annual Design Show, 1976 (Box 34, Folder 22)
    - Dept. of Cinema Studies - memos, D. Oppenheim/T. Perry; Perry/ anyone, 1974-1975 (Box 35, Folder 1)
      bar code#: 3 1142 04226086 2
    - Dept. of Cinema Studies - memos, D. Oppenheim to/from Bill Simon, Robert Sklar, 1976-1977 (Box 35, Folder 2)
    - Dept. of Cinema Studies - memos to/from Robert Sklar, 1976-1978 (Box 35, Folder 3)
    - Dept. of Dance - memos to/from Stuart Hodes, 1976-1978 (Box 35, Folder 4)
    - Dept. of Dance - "A First Decade Dance Showcase", 2/10/77, 1977 (Box 35, Folder 5)
    - Dept. of Directing - memos D. Oppenheim/Carl Weber; Weber/anyone, 1975-1976 (Box 35, Folder 6)
    - Dept. of Film and T.V., Undergrad, 1975-1976 (Box 35, Folder 7)
    - Dept. of Film and T.V., Undergrad - Media Internship Program, (Prof. Falk), 1975-1976 (Box 35, Folder 8)
    - Dept. of Film and T.V., Undergrad - memos, 1975-1976 (Box 35, Folder 9)
    - Dept. of Film and T.V., Undergrad - memos, Jan.1977-Mar.1977 (Box 35, Folder 10)
    - Dept. of Film and T.V, Undergrad. - memos, Apr., 1977-Sep 1977 (Box 35, Folder 11)
    - Dept. of Film and T.V., Undergrad - memos, D. Oppenheim /Haig Manoogian; Manoogian/anyone, 1975-1976 (Box 35, Folder 12)
    - Dept. of Film and Television, Graduate, 1976-1977 (Box 35, Folder 13)
    - Dept. of Film and T.V., Graduate - memos, D. Oppenheim/Mel Howard Howard/anyone, 1975-1976 (Box 35, Folder 14)
    - Dept. of Film and T.V., Graduate - Student review, 1976 (Box 35, Folder 15)
    - Department of Film and T.V., Graduate - Search for Chair, 1976 (Box 35, Folder 16)
    - Documentary Fund for Independent Film Video Makers, 1977 (Box 35, Folder 17)
    - Executive Committee, SOA, Nov 1976-Mar 1977 (Box 35, Folder 18)
    - Executive Committee, SOA, Apr 1977-Nov 1977 (Box 35, Folder 19)
    - Entering Students, Fall, 1976 (Box 35, Folder 20)
    - Faculty Committee on Graduate Certification, 1975 (Box 35, Folder 21)
    - Faculty Names and Statistics, 1975-1976 (Box 35, Folder 22)
    - Faculty Unionization, 1976 (Box 35, Folder 23)
    - Films by SOA Students (misc. materials), 1976 (Box 36, Folder 1)
      bar code#: 3 1142 04226087 0
    - Film Festival, NYU Students, (34th, 35th, 36th, 37th annual), 1974-1977 (Box 36, Folder 2)
    - Film Society of Lincoln Center, Board of Directors, 1975-1976 (Box 36, Folder 3)
    - Film Society of Lincoln Center, New York Film Festival (12th, 13th, 14th, 15th annual), 1974-1977 (Box 36, Folder 4)
    - Form Letters, Student Acceptances, June, 1973 (Box 36, Folder 5)
    - Freshman Receptions, Office of the Dean, 1976-1977 (Box 36, Folder 6)
    - F.Y.I. (misc. correspondence to D. Oppenheim), 1977 (Box 36, Folder 7)
    - G - General, 1975-1976 (Box 36, Folder 8)
    - Gallatin, Advisory Board, D. Oppenheim Chair, Feb 1976-Aug 1976 (Box 36, Folder 9)
    - Gallatin, Advisory Board, D. Oppenheim Chair, Sep 1976-Dec 1977 (Box 36, Folder 10)
    - Graduate Commission, 1975 (Box 36, Folder 11)
    - Graduate Commission, 1976 (Box 36, Folder 12)
    - Grants and Gifts, Janet Grinnell (Development Director), 1974-1977 (Box 36, Folder 13)
    - Grants and Gifts, Janet Grinnell (Development Director), 1978 (Box 36, Folder 14)
    - Grants and Gifts, (Alphabetized by Donor), 1975-1978 (Box 36, Folder 15)
    - Grievance Committee, SOA, 1971-1975 (Box 36, Folder 16)
    - Grotowski, Jerzy, Lecture at NYU, Dec.1970 (Box 36, Folder 17)
    - Grotowski, Jerzy, 1971-1975 (Box 36, Folder 18)
    - Guskin, Harold, Department of Acting, 1974-1976 (Box 36, Folder 19)
    - H - General, 1975-1976 (Box 36, Folder 20)
    - Incoming FYI + Routing, Jan 1976-Apr 1976 (Box 37, Folder 1)
      bar code#: 3 1142 04226088 8
    - Incoming FYI + Routing, May 1976-Aug 1976 (Box 37, Folder 2)
    - Incoming FYI + Routing, Sep 1976-Dec 1976 (Box 37, Folder 3)
    - Incoming Memoranda - Deans, Administrators, Offices, 01/76-08/76, 1976 (Box 37, Folder 4)
    - Incoming Memoranda - Deans, Administrators, Offices, 09/76-03/77, 1976-1977 (Box 37, Folder 5)
    - Inquiry Letters - SOA responses, form letters, procedures, 1974-1976 (Box 37, Folder 6)
    - Inquiry Letters - Pre-College Dance Program, 1975 (Box 37, Folder 7)
    - Interactive Telecommunications - MFA Proposal, Martin Elton: Communication and Change: Preliminary Study, 1975-1977 (Box 37, Folder 8)
    - Interactive Telecommunications - Masters Proposal, Memos, 1975-1977 (Box 37, Folder 9)
    - Interactive Telecommunications - Progress Report, M. Elton, 1976 (Box 37, Folder 10)
    - Interactive Telecommunications - Masters at SOA, 05/77-10/77, 1977 (Box 37, Folder 11)
    - Interactive Telecommunications - Proposal for M.A. Program in Non Broadcast Telecommunications, Jan. 1977 (Box 37, Folder 12)
    - Interactive Telecommunications - Proposal for MFA, Jun-Sept. 1977 (Box 37, Folder 13)
    - Library - Elmer Holmes Bobst, Uses of Space, 1976 (Box 37, Folder 14)
    - Admissions Responses, Reception for Applicants, 1973-1974 (Box 38, Folder 1)
      bar code#: 3 1142 04226089 6
    - Budget Policy Advisory Committee Report, 1974 (Box 38, Folder 2)
    - Gitlow, Dean College of Business + Public Administration, 1972, 1974 (Box 38, Folder 3)
    - Graduate School of Arts and Science, Memos, D. Oppenheim, 1968-1974 (Box 38, Folder 4)
    - Hester, J. Pres., Review of Oppenheim's activities as Dean, 1974 (Box 38, Folder 5)
    - Independent Filmakers, c., 1973 (Box 38, Folder 6)
    - Internships, 1973 (Box 38, Folder 7)
    - Jameson Advertising Inc., 1974 (Box 38, Folder 8)
    - Kennedy, E., Dean of Libraries, (library-SOA corresp.), 1969-1974 (Box 38, Folder 9)
    - Koenigsberg, Sylvia, Correspondence to/from D. Oppenheim, 1973 (Box 38, Folder 10)
    - League of Professional Theatre Training Programs, Status Report on the Theatre Program, 1972 (Box 38, Folder 11)
    - Likens, John, resignation, 1974 (Box 38, Folder 12)
    - Master File, Undergrad. Film and T.V (UGFTV), 1974 (Box 38, Folder 13)
    - McKay, R., Dean School of Law, Corresp. to/from D.Oppenheim, 1974 (Box 38, Folder 14)
    - McNamara, Brooks, 1974-1976 (Box 38, Folder 15)
    - Media Plan, George J. Walsh + Co. Advertising, 1973-1974 (Box 38, Folder 16)
    - Miller, Michael, 1974 (Box 38, Folder 17)
    - Minority Student Award Committee, 1973-1974 (Box 38, Folder 18)
    - New Building, Plans and Sketches, 1973-1974 (Box 38, Folder 19)
    - News Bureau - Corresp., Press Releases, Newspaper Ads., 1971-1972 (Box 38, Folder 20)
    - News Bureau - Corresp., Press Releases, Newspaper Ads., 1973 (Box 38, Folder 21)
    - News Bureau - Corresp., Press Releases, Newspaper Ads., 1974-1975 (Box 38, Folder 22)
    - NYU Club, Correspondence to/from D. Oppenheim, 1972-1974 (Box 38, Folder 23)
    - NYU Press, Chris Kentra (Director), 1970 (Box 38, Folder 24)
    - Office Supplies, 1975 (Box 38, Folder 25)
    - Organization Committee, SOA, 1975 (Box 38, Folder 26)
    - Payrole, incl. "Special" Employees, 1974 (Box 38, Folder 27)
    - Personnel, 1973-1974 (Box 38, Folder 28)
    - Photography, History of Course, 1975 (Box 38, Folder 29)
    - Post Graduate Employment Department, 1973 (Box 38, Folder 30)
    - Proposal for a Doctoral Program in Cinema Studies, George Amberg, Chair Dept. Cinema, 1970 (Box 38, Folder 31)
    - Proposal for a Doctoral Program in Dance, 1974 (Box 38, Folder 32)
    - Publicity, 1969-1974 (Box 38, Folder 33)
    - Ramsay, Louise, Assistant Dean, 1974 (Box 38, Folder 34)
    - Regents Regional Co-Ordinating Council for Post-Secondary Education in NYC: Ad Hoc Comm't on Performing Arts Education - SubCom't on Data Analysis, 1973-1974 (Box 38, Folder 35)
    - Regents Regional Co-ordinating Council for Post-Secondary Education in NYC; Ad Hoc Comm't on Performing Arts -Questionnaires, 1974 (Box 38, Folder 36)
    - Registration Statistics, Fall 1973, Summer 1974 and Fall 1974, 1973-1974 (Box 38, Folder 37)
    - Reservation Contracts for NYU Facilities, Book Requisitions, 1974 (Box 38, Folder 38)
    - S - General, 1974 (Box 38, Folder 39)
    - Space Allocations and Reservations, 1969-1974 (Box 38, Folder 40)
    - Statewide Master Plan, 1971-1974 (Box 38, Folder 41)
    - Summer Sessions, 1974-1975 (Box 38, Folder 42)
    - Telephone - Analysis of Toll Calls, Sep 1973-May 1974 (Box 38, Folder 43)
    - Telephone - Analysis of Toll Calls, 1974 (Box 38, Folder 44)
    - Theatre Program, 1974-1975 (Box 38, Folder 45)
    - Young Audiences, Minutes, Meetings, Evaluation Report, 1969-1971 (Box 38, Folder 46)
    - Addresses, Telephone Numbers, 1973-1975 (Box 39, Folder 1)
      bar code#: 3 1142 04226090 4
    - Annual Faculty Activity Report, Dept. Drama, Design Dept., 1973-1974 (Box 39, Folder 2)
    - Anthology Film Archives (incl. Film Art Fund + By-laws), 1973-1974 (Box 39, Folder 3)
    - Appointment of Faculty to NYU Committees, 1973 (Box 39, Folder 4)
    - Arts Development Assoc. - Questionnaires and Responses, Nov., 1973 (Box 39, Folder 5)
    - Arts Development Assoc. - Questionnaires and Responses, Nov., 1973 (Box 39, Folder 6)
    - Arts Development Assoc. - Questionnaires and Responses, Nov., 1973 (Box 39, Folder 7)
    - Arts Development Assoc. - Questionnaires and Responses, (not tabulated) Nov., 1973 (Box 39, Folder 8)
    - Arts Development Assoc.- Questionnaires and Responses, (not tabulated) Nov., 1973 (Box 39, Folder 9)
    - Arts Development Assoc. - Questionnaires and Responses, SOA c1973 (Box 39, Folder 10)
    - Arts Development Assoc. - Tabulations for Nov. 1973 Questionnaire (Box 39, Folder 11)
    - Arts Management + Administration Program, 1974 (Box 39, Folder 12)
    - Oppenheim meetings with Chancellor Borowitz, 1974 (Box 39, Folder 13)
    - Budgets (restricted), 1969-1974 (Box 39, Folder 14)
    - Budget Advisory Committee, 1974 (Box 39, Folder 15)
    - Budget Policy Advisory Committee Report, 06/15/74, 1974 (Box 39, Folder 16)
    - Calendar - events, meetings, schedules, 1971-1975 (Box 39, Folder 17)
    - Calendars for the Academic Year, '69/70 and '75/76, 1969, 1975 (Box 39, Folder 18)
    - Chancellor's Meetings, 1973, 1974 (Box 39, Folder 19)
    - Cinema Studies - Questionnaires and Responses c., 1973 (Box 39, Folder 20)
    - Circle in the Square Contract, 1974 (Box 39, Folder 21)
    - Comm't on Faculty Organization/Comm't on Org. Policy, 1969-1974 (Box 39, Folder 22)
    - Consortia Arrangement Responses, Memos from D. Oppenheim, Hodes, Kirby, Oliva; Oppenheim to Dept. Chairs, 1973 (Box 39, Folder 23)
    - Demers, Danielle (Admin. Director, Theatre Program), 1972-1974 (Box 39, Folder 24)
    - Dept. Chairmen's Meetings, 1971-1974 (Box 39, Folder 25)
    - Dept. of Cinema Studies, Curriculum, non-NYU Budgets, 1973-1974 (Box 39, Folder 26)
    - Dept. of Cinema Studies, Questionnaires and Responses, 1973 (Box 39, Folder 27)
    - Dept. of Film and T.V., Graduate and Undergrad, 1969-1974 (Box 39, Folder 28)
    - Eugene, Joseph, 1974 (Box 39, Folder 29)
    - Expenditure Control Reports, 1974 (Box 39, Folder 30)
    - Faculty Appointment Letters, 1974 (Box 39, Folder 32)
    - Faculty Salaries, 1973-1975 (Box 39, Folder 32)
    - Fundraising, 1973 (Box 39, Folder 33)
    - Goals Committee (SOA), 1974 (Box 39, Folder 34)
    - Grants - Proposal to Establish a Communications Center, 1971 (Box 39, Folder 35)
    - Incoming FYI to Dean Oppenheim, 1974-1975 (Box 39, Folder 36)
    - International Council of Fine Arts, 1974 (Box 39, File 37)
    - Performing Arts, Sub-Committee/Ad Hoc Committee, 1973 (Box 39, Folder 38)
    - Performing Arts, Sub-Committee/Ad Hoc Committee, 1974 (Box 39, Folder 39)
    - Back-up Materials, Fact Sheets, Reports, Minutes, etc..., 1975 (Box 40, Folder 1)
      bar code#: 3 1142 04226091 2
    - Balis, Andrea, Artistic Director, Section Ten, 1975 (Box 40, Folder 2)
    - Blueprints, Mar 1975 (Box 40, Folder 3)
    - Circus, 1979-1980 (Box 40, Folder 4)
    - Dept. of Cinema Studies, Nov 1975-Aug 1978 (Box 40, Folder 5)
    - Dept. of Drama, Graduate, Sept., Sep 1976-Aug 1978 (Box 40, Folder 6)
    - Dept. of Drama, Graduate, Restructuring I, Oct 1976-Jun 1977 (Box 40, Folder 7)
    - Dept. of Drama, Graduate, Restructuring II, Feb 1977-Sep 1977 (Box 40, Folder 8)
    - Dept. of Drama, Graduate, Restructuring III, Oct 1977-Feb 1978 (Box 40, Folder 9)
    - Dept. of Drama, Graduate, T. Hoffman, Chair, Sep 1978-Jun 1980 (Box 40, Folder 10)
    - Dept. of Drama, Undergrad., S. Flakes, Chair, 1975-1976 (Box 40, Folder 11)
    - Dept. of Drama, Undergrad., Y. Simonides, Chair, 1976-1979 (Box 40, Folder 12)
    - Dept. of Film and T.V., Graduate, Jun 1975-Aug 1976 (Box 40, Folder 13)
    - Dept. of Film and T.V., Graduate, Sep 1976-Jul 1978 (Box 40, Folder 14)
    - Dept. of Film and T.V., Undergrad, (UGFTV), Oct 1975-Jun 1977 (Box 40, Folder 15)
    - Dept. of Film and T.V., Undergrad, (UGFTV), Sep 1977-Jul 1979 (Box 40, Folder 16)
    - Dept. of Film and T.V., Undergrad, (UGFTV), Enrollment, 1977-1979 (Box 40, Folder 17)
    - Hill, Carol, 1974-1976 (Box 40, Folder 18)
    - Interactive Telecommunications, 1977 (Box 40, Folder 19)
    - Interactive Telecommunications, 1978 (Box 40, Folder 20)
    - Interactive Telecommunications, Proposals and Appendices, 1977 (Box 40, Folder 21)
    - Oliva, L. J., Vice Chancellor Academic Planning & Services, 1974-1976 (Box 40, Folder 22)
    - P - General, 1975-1979 (Box 40, Folder 23)
    - Phillips, Peter, Master Teacher of Perception, 1975-1976 (Box 40, Folder 24)
    - Photography Program Proposal, Thomas Drysdale, Mar 31, 1977 (Box 40, Folder 25)
    - Proposals for Courses/Programs, 1975-1976 (Box 40, Folder 26)
    - Publicity (mostly newspaper clippings), 1975 (Box 40, Folder 27)
    - Publicity (mostly newspaper clippings), 1976-1977 (Box 40, Folder 28)
    - Publicity - News Bureau, NYU Press Office, Clipbook Summary, 1975-1976 (Box 40, Folder 29)
    - Ramsay, Louise, Assistant Dean, SOA, Memoranda, 1975 (Box 41, Folder 1)
      bar code#: 3 1142 04226092 0
    - Ramsay, Louise, Assistant Dean, SOA, Memoranda, 1976 (Box 41, Folder 2)
    - Returning and Non-Returning Students, Fall 1976 (Box 41, Folder 3)
    - S - General, 1975-1976 (Box 41, Folder 4)
    - Saltzman, Jared (student), 1974-1975 (Box 41, Folder 5)
    - Sawhill, J., memos to/from D. Oppenheim, Dean's Meetings, 1975-1977 (Box 41, Folder 6)
    - Schechner, Richard, Prof. of Drama, 1974-1976 (Box 41, Folder 7)
    - Sebazco, Raul (student), 1976-1977 (Box 41, Folder 8)
    - Senate, memos to/from D. Oppenheim, 1975-1978 (Box 41, Folder 9)
    - Sherman, Barry, Lecturer in Film, 1975-1976 (Box 41, Folder 10)
    - Society for Cinema Studies, Annual Meeting, April, Apr 1975 (Box 41, Folder 11)
    - Society of Fellows, 1977-1979 (Box 41, Folder 12)
    - Special Students - Loans, Financial Aid, Debts, 1976-1978 (Box 41, Folder 13)
      (restricted)
    - Special Students - Incomplete Courses, Grade Changes, Dismissal etc..., 1975-1979 (Box 41, Folder 14)
    - Special Students, 1976-1979 (Box 41, Folder 15)
    - Sponsored Programs, Nancy Greenberg, Director, 1974-1976 (Box 41, Folder 16)
    - Sponsored Programs, Nancy Greenberg, Director, 1977-1978 (Box 41, Folder 17)
    - Sponsored Programs, SOA Applications as Submitted by NYU, 1975-1977 (Box 41, Folder 18)
    - Sponsored Programs, Sponsored Research + Training Statisitc Reports, 1975-1976 (Box 41, Folder 19)
    - Student Affairs Co-Ordinator, Maria Myers, 1979 (Box 41, Folder 20)
    - Student Conduct, NYU Rules for, c., 1970s (Box 41, Folder 21)
    - Student Records and Registration, SOA Recorders Office, 1975-1976 (Box 41, Folder 22)
    - Sussman, Risa, 1975-1979 (Box 41, Folder 23)
    - TDR (The Drama Review), 1974-1975 (Box 41, Folder 24)
    - Telephones, Analysis of Toll Calls, 1975 (Box 41, Folder 25)